<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Five Things You Didnt Know</string>
    <string name="header">ABOUT KRAMER ELECTRONICS LTD </string>
    <string name="provider_name">com.facts.provider</string>
    <string name="solution_header">KRAMER SOLUTIONS </string>
    <string name="products_header">KRAMER PRODUCTS </string>
    <string name="events_header">KRAMER EVENTS </string>
    <string name="world_header">KRAMER ON THE WORLD </string>
    <string name="location_header">KRAMER LOCATION</string>
    <string name="literature_header">KRAMER LITERATURE </string>
    <string name="solution_content">Sorry , nothing interesting for this fact.. cha cha cha </string>
    <string name="products_content">Today, we have a line of over 1,000 products. Every one of them was developed through extensive R D and customer feedback. This is what keeps Kramer Electronics ahead. Listening to, and acting on, customer feedback sets our products apart from others. We have built our reputation on this. </string>
    <string name="events_content">Come meet us in one of the many trade shows we’re presenting in around the US and worldwide. </string>
    <string name="world_content">KRAMER ON THE WORLD </string>
    <string name="literature_content">Uploading brochures with open spread, that do not make sense to someone who sees it the first time, is not the right way to distribute our literature. </string>
    <string name="location_content">A personal connection with our customers is crucial to our success. We have offices all over the world able to serve the local market, with local support and expertise. Today, there are over one million Kramer Electronics products in use worldwide. Every two minutes, a Kramer product is sold somewhere around the world. Every product carries our personal guarantee and service commitment. Our team stands behind every product we sell – even years after it is installed. We now offer a seven-year warranty on all Kramer products, covering parts and labor.</string>
    <string name="training_header">Kramer Online Training</string>
    <string name="training_content"> Kramer Academy also offers Web based training. Whether it is just not possible to get everyone together, or if online training is an important part of your educational programs, Kramer can provide you the online Web based training you need. Any of our long-form programs can be condensed into a webinar or series of webinars.</string>
</resources>
